{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "A friend tells you the name of a new restaurant, and she spells it for you. You don't write it all down, so you ask her: '___ you spell it again, please?'\n",
            "a": "Would",
            "b": "Should",
            "c": "Might",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "A friend arrives at your flat. He's very hot and thirsty. You ask: '___ you like a glass of water?'\n",
            "a": "Would",
            "b": "Could",
            "c": "Should",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I _________ on television next month. The TV company were filming our hospital today for a programme about young doctors.\n",
            "a": "can be",
            "b": "could be",
            "c": "could have been",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why didn't you tell me that you wanted a sandwich? I ___ one for you when I made mine.\n",
            "a": "can't have made",
            "b": "could have made",
            "c": "could make",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm so hungry, I ___ a horse!\n",
            "a": "would eat",
            "b": "could have eaten",
            "c": "could eat",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sue used to ___ speak Arabic fluently, but she's forgotten a lot of it now.\n",
            "a": "be able to",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "can",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "When Helen and Sue started their business, they didn't have much experience, but they ___ persuade the bank to lend them some money.\n",
            "a": "had better",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "were able to",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We'll _________ clean the flat before Emma comes. It's quite dirty.\n",
            "a": "must",
            "b": "have to",
            "c": "should",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ben _________ walk to work. He could get the bus, but he walks because he likes the exercise.\n",
            "a": "doesn't have to",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "can't",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Anna ___ Daniel your phone number. She doesn't know him.\n",
            "a": "couldn't have given",
            "b": "may not have given",
            "c": "might not have given",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "20",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}